[grave music]
Please don't kill--
[gasps]
Please don't kill me.
My daughter is very sick.
[groans]
[No-eul] Close your eyes.
If you want to live, do as I say.
[scanner beeps]
[woman on PA] Player 246, eliminated.
SQUID GAME 3
EPISODE 1
KEYS AND KNIVES
[masked soldier] Take it away.
Finally decide to be a good girl, did we?
This is new.
[No-eul] I gave it some thought.
Since they're going to die anyway,
using their organs to save others
isn't such a bad idea.
[masked soldier laughs]
[masked soldier] Good thinking.
I'm glad you finally came around.
[No-eul] Show me around.
[masked soldier] Where?
[No-eul] The workroom.
[masked soldier] What for?
[No-eul] You and I are
in the same boat now, aren't we?
We don't want any secrets between us.
[alarm buzzing]
[eerie music]
[door closes]
[gasps]
Is he dead?
He's alive.
Help me get him on the bed.
-Quickly.
-[Yong-sik] Okay.
[Geum-ja] Here. To the bed.
[mercenary] He's nowhere around the boat.
How much did he drink last night?
Not enough to be wasted.
I counted the empty bottles inside.
There were quite a few.
He could have come outside to puke
and fallen in.
The boat was rocking a lot last night.
Maybe that's what I heard
in the middle of the night?
What did you hear?
I heard someone outside, some thrashing.
What time was it?
It was around 3 a.m., wasn't it?
Yeah, around then.
[Woo-seok] So I went outside,
and Captain Park was already there.
We should've woken everyone up
and gone looking for him.
Let's search the area first.
[Captain] But Detective Hwang.
The currents are strong here.
He probably drifted pretty far overnight.
If he got drunk and fell overboard,
there's no chance he's alive.
Are you going to waste time
looking for a corpse?
You said you have to find the island
in three or four days.
Let's go to the nearest port
and get another drone operator.
Let's get going.
[ominous music]
[In-ho] Let's attack them first.
[Gi-hun] That doesn't mean
we should kill each other.
That's exactly what they want us to do.
[In-ho] A small sacrifice
for the greater good?
[Gi-hun] Even if it takes a sacrifice,
we must put an end to this game now.
[Jung-bae] Fight with us
so we can go home together.
[Gi-hun] Anyone who wishes to join us,
please step forward.
[Jung-bae] Why did you bring me
instead of Young-il?
-[Gi-hun] Because you're my friend.
-[Gi-hun's voice echoing]
[Geum-ja shakily] Sir?
[tense music]
Oh, gosh, sir?
You're alive.
Thank God you're alive.
Are you all right?
What about the others?
And Jung-bae?
[sinister music]
[Front Man] Look closely
at the consequences
of your little hero game.
[Jung-bae] Gi-hun.
[gunshot]
[dark music]
[breath trembling]
[alarm buzzing]
-[door closes]
-[remote beeps]
[ceiling rumbles]
[digital trilling]
[masked manager] A total of 35 players
were eliminated last night,
and 60 players remain in the game.
The prize money accumulated
up to this point is 39.6 billion won,
and each person's share
is 660 million won.
You will now take a vote to decide
whether to continue the games or not.
[footsteps approaching]
Why did you keep me alive?
Why didn't you kill me?
Answer me! Tell me why!
Why did you let me live? Why?
Shoot me, you bastards!
Yes, shoot me! Kill me too!
Why did you let me live?
[screaming] What do you want from me?
Why didn't you kill me?
You won!
So go ahead and kill me!
-I'm begging you, just kill me!
-[phone ringing]
We're back at the port for now.
The plan is to find another drone operator
and head back out.
Don't let them find the island
until the games are over.
[Captain] Yes, sir.
Detective Hwang!
Give me a call when you're ready to go.
-Okay.
-[Captain] Watch your step.
What should I do if things go south?
Kill them all.
Including the detective.
[somber music]
[masked manager]
You will now vote again to decide
whether to continue the games or not.
The vote will again be held
in reverse order of your player numbers.
Player 456, please cast your vote.
If you don't show an intent to vote
by the count of three,
your vote will be considered
an abstention.
One, two, three.
Player 456 forfeited his vote,
so it will be counted as an abstention.
Next, Player 448. Please cast your vote.
[man 1] We're not going to hurt you,
so vote freely.
[man 2] Yeah, do whatever you want.
[man 3] Don't mind us,
feel free to vote however you want.
[beeps]
[elevator door closes]
[Masked Officer]
The casualties have been identified,
eight managers and 27 soldiers.
[Front Man] Replace the dead soldiers
with workers
and repair the damaged facility
as soon as possible.
The VIPs will be arriving soon.
[Masked Officer] Yes, sir.
[ominous music]
[forklift beeping]
[loud thud]
[masked soldier]
Where did you learn to shoot?
Ah.
I heard women serve in the military
in North Korea.
Did you learn there?
[No-eul] Yes.
[masked soldier]
What made you cross the border?
Were you starving up there?
Or perhaps,
you got into serious trouble?
[masked soldier sighs]
You said we were in the same boat now.
Shouldn't we get to know
each other better?
[No-eul] Once this is over,
let's meet up, just you and me.
I'll tell you then.
[masked soldier sighs]
I don't want to wait that long.
There's a nice spot for a date here.
Do you want to stop by?
[No-eul] It's a long story.
Let me see the workroom first.
[masked soldier] All right.
I know a little spot downstairs.
You'll like it too.
[masked soldier laughs]
[masked manager] In accordance
with your free and democratic vote,
we will proceed
with the next game tomorrow.
Thank you.
-[alarm buzzing]
-[door opens]
[door closes]
[Jeong-dae] Hey, 456.
Tell me.
Was this all just part of your plan?
You staged a rebellion to lure people out
and had them all
killed at once, didn't you?
But he was all like,
"Kill me!"
-[players laugh]
-Was that just for show?
Man, he creeps me out.
That's right.
Instead of killing him like the others,
they brought him back here.
There's definitely something going on.
Anyway, thanks to you taking out the reds
and getting them all killed,
the money went up,
-and we won the vote by a landslide.
-[Yeong-sam chuckles]
Everyone, let's thank him
with a big round of applause.
[man 1] Thank you very much!
[man 2] I see you were
one of us all along.
[Seon-nyeo] You fool.
What did I tell you?
You're not here of your own free will.
Those vengeful souls hovering
over your head brought you here.
[eerie music]
Do you hear them?
Your friends screaming right in your ears.
You can cover them all you want,
but it won't help.
Those screams will only get louder.
You will be hearing their screams
until the moment you die.
[laughing]
[Seon-nyeo groans]
-[Player 006] Let go of her!
-[Player 306] Let her go!
[Player 306 straining]
[loud crash]
[Player 006] Are you all right, ma'am?
[Gi-hun, Seon-nyeo breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
How does it look?
[doctor] We'll be able to get
some good bits.
[eerie music]
[man 1] Slowly.
One, two, three!
[door opens]
[man 2] Relax. Don't worry.
Number 011 is one of us now.
We brought you a good one, didn't we?
That's her gift to us.
Why did you bring her here?
We're in the same boat now.
Isn't it nice to get to know each other?
The ones who were here before us
ended up in deep shit
because they didn't trust each other
and kept secrets.
But we trust each other,
so there shouldn't be any secrets.
That's why we agreed
to keep our masks off in here.
Isn't that right?
[man 1 sighs]
[doctor] So you're Number 011?
Do you realize how much fucking money
we've lost because of you?
[man 1] There's no time for that.
We have to move fast to make it on time.
Get to work.
[man 2] Come here.
I'll show you how it's done
from the start.
That's your gift right there.
He's still alive, right?
[doctor] Yeah, just unconscious.
All right. Let's open up
Number 011's gift now, shall we?
-[groans]
-[tense music]
-[doctor] What is it?
-Stop.
[doctor] What… What the…
Put the knife down.
-[doctor] Okay.
-Hey, what the hell?
[No-eul] Step back.
[man 2] Aren't you one of us now?
[man 1] You psycho bitch!
[man 2 screams]
[No-eul grunts]
[man 2 groans]
[man 1 groans]
[breathes heavily]
-[gunshot]
-[man 2 gasps]
[breath trembles]
You wanna know why
I came down from the North?
My commander was a lot like you,
and I put a bullet in his head.
-[snickers]
-[ominous music]
Don't kill me. I'm not with these guys.
I just came here for the money.
[No-eul] Save this man.
If he dies, you do too.
[mysterious music]
[Myung-gi] Jun-hee.
You like sweet potatoes.
[Geum-ja] Sir.
You should eat,
even if it's just a little.
Look, I know.
I know that
you were trying to save us all.
You were trying to punish the bad guys
and put an end to all this.
[dark music]
I'm sorry.
I should've found a way
to bring back the magazines.
You have nothing
to apologize for, Hyun-ju.
It's all Dae-ho's fault.
I saw it, my mom saw it,
and everyone else saw it.
Dae-ho came to pick up the magazines,
but when he was about to leave,
he just sank to the floor.
When Hyun-ju came to get them,
the masked men barged in.
If my mom hadn't stopped her,
she would've died too.
Isn't that right, Hyun-ju?
[Geum-ja] This won't bring anyone back.
Those of us who are still alive
have to keep going, don't you think?
Make sure you eat, okay?
Don't choke. Drink some water with it too.
Gosh, he's completely out of it.
[eerie music]
NOVEMBER 4 - DAY 4 OF THE SEARCH
[knocking on door]
[Woo-seok] Hwang, are you asleep?
No, not yet.
Hey, since you're still up,
can we talk for a bit over a drink?
Sure, come in.
No, I'm good.
Oh, all right.
[Woo-seok exhales]
So, what did you want to talk about?
Right.
Well,
it's about Captain Park.
You said he saved you
when you almost drowned, right?
Yeah, I got shot on an island
and fell into the sea.
He rescued me and took me to the hospital.
Anything else you remember?
I just woke up at the hospital,
and my mom told me about Captain Park.
Why?
[laughs awkwardly]
Well, the thing is,
I told you I heard some noises last night
and went outside, right?
Yes, Captain Park also heard some noises.
I didn't think much of it at the time,
but it looked like
he was holding something in his hand.
What was it?
A screwdriver.
[Woo-seok] Who's there?
-[Captain] Choi, is that you?
-[eerie music]
It's me, Captain Park.
A screwdriver?
Yeah.
It was dark, but I definitely saw him
holding a screwdriver.
Think about it. Isn't that strange?
Why was he holding that?
Maybe he'd been doing some work.
But I think he said
he was trying to sleep when he came out.
Or maybe he grabbed a weapon
just to be safe.
You think so?
-But still, it's--
-[Jun-ho] Look.
Do you think he has something to do
with the drone operator's disappearance?
I have good instincts
for this kind of thing,
and there's something fishy
about Captain Park--
He saved my life,
and he's been helping me
search for the island for years.
He still is, even now.
I know that.
I'm not saying
he did something to the drone operator.
I just have a bad--
You had a drink with the drone operator
last night as well, didn't you?
Well, yeah.
But not much, just a few drinks.
[chuckles awkwardly]
We're setting out early in the morning.
You should go get some sleep.
Right, okay.
And starting tomorrow,
no more drinking on the boat.
All right.
[eerie music]
[indistinct mumbling]
[warped classical music playing
on speakers]
[eerie music]
-[alarm buzzing]
-[woman on PA] The fourth game
will begin momentarily.
Please follow
the instructions from our staff.
["The Blue Danube" playing on speakers]
[Masked Officer] Captain.
The VIPs have arrived.
[music intensifies]
[woman on PA] You are witnessing the fate
of those who refused
the democratic process of voting
and instead attempted to stop the game
using violent means.
We will not tolerate
any irrational behavior
-which attempts to destroy
-[Dae-ho coughs]
the fair rules of this game,
and such actions will be punished
in accordance with our strict standards.
We thank you again for your cooperation.
[eerie music]
[woman on PA] Welcome to your fourth game.
This game will be played in two teams.
Before we start the game,
you will divide into teams.
Please take turns drawing a ball
from the gumball machine in front of you.
The bullet didn't hit
any major organs or blood vessels.
I stitched up his wound, but…
But?
He's lost too much blood.
He needs a transfusion,
but there's no blood.
Use mine.
What's your blood type?
Type O.
That should work just fine.
-[mechanical clicking]
-[mysterious music]
[mechanical clicking]
It's okay. We don't even know
what game it is yet.
[mechanical clicking]
[ball clatters]
[dark music]
Any funny business, and you're dead.
[masked manager] The game
you will be playing is Hide-and-seek.
[players] Hide-and-seek?
[masked manager] The Blue Team
must either find the exit
and escape within 30 minutes
or stay hidden from the Red Team
until the time is up.
[man] What about the taggers?
Just like when we played this as kids,
all we need to do is find the ones hiding?
[masked manager]
The Red Team, the taggers,
must find members of the Blue Team
and kill them within 30 minutes.
-[players murmuring]
-[dark music]
Kill them?
[masked manager] That is correct.
The Red Team must find
the Blue Team and kill them.
If you fail to kill any opposing players,
you will be eliminated.
Those people are going to kill us?
That is correct.
[Yong-sik, Geum-ja breathes shakily]
What is this?
[masked manager] You have been given keys
to doors in the arena.
You can use that key
to go through the doors,
but once a door is unlocked,
it cannot be relocked.
[Yeong-sam] So they can hide somewhere
and use their keys to escape.
They have it so much easier!
-That's right!
-So much easier.
On top of that,
we have to kill those people.
And with our bare hands.
That's right. This isn't fair.
It's not like they will just roll over
and ask us to kill them.
How do you expect us
to kill someone with our bare hands?
[masked manager]
We understand your concerns.
That's why we've prepared
a small gift for the Red Team as well.
Please open the box and check.
Thank you.
[players murmuring]
Oh, wow.
[Nam-gyu gasps]
[Nam-gyu exclaims in awe]
[masked manager] The Red Team can use
knives to attack the Blue Team.
However, members of the Red Team
are not allowed to attack each other.
[Jeong-dae] Shouldn't you give us
a shield or something?
You give them knives
and expect us to just run around unarmed?
He's right.
You've got to give us something too.
Yes, all we have is a key.
That's not fair!
[Player 203] But you can use the key
to open a door and escape.
[Player 312] That's right.
[Yeong-sam] Just hide somewhere.
It should be a piece of cake!
[man] That's right. You have it easier.
Brother.
That's what you're good at.
Hiding like a rat.
[masked manager] Before we start the game,
we will give you one last chance
to change your fate.
If any of you
are not happy with your role,
you may switch roles
with someone on the opposing team
before the game starts.
[Jeong-dae] What? We can switch roles?
That is correct.
You can swap your items and vests
upon mutual agreement.
But once the game starts,
removing or trading your vests
will be strictly prohibited.
Please make your choice carefully.
[breath trembles]
[eerie music]
Everyone, this is the new drone operator.
[drone pilot] Nice to meet you all.
[Kim] It was hard to get him here,
so treat him well.
[mercenaries] Yes, sir.
[drone pilot] Thank you.
All right,
-put on a life jacket first.
-[phone buzzing]
We don't want any more accidents.
-I guess you heard?
-[drone pilot] Oh, yes.
Where are you?
Hurry, we're about to leave.
[Woo-seok] Hwang, go ahead.
I'm not coming with you.
What are you talking about?
[Woo-seok] There's something
I have to look into.
Are you still going on about this?
My gut feeling is usually right.
I'll call you if I find anything.
Be careful around that prick Captain Park.
[Jun-ho] Mr. Choi…
[Captain] All right, let's get going now.
-Let's go.
-All right.
What on earth possessed you
to show up here out of the blue
and get me out so early in the morning?
I've been swamped with work,
and I'm exhausted.
The boss is dead.
What?
He's dead? What happened?
It's a long story.
Wait, then why didn't you call me?
Just because
I'm on the straight and narrow now--
It's not like that. He was…
You know
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Minus One, right?
-Yeah.
-He and I played it, and…
Yeah. He just needed to minus the other…
Never mind.
Let's just go have some hangover soup.
Finish your story. So what happened?
Start the car. I'll tell you on the way.
-I don't get you at all.
-[engine starts]
How does someone die
by playing Rock, Paper, Scissors?
None of you can get out of here alive.
[woman] Then, what should I…
Only I, shaman of the sea,
can guide you to the path of life.
-[woman] We believe in you, ma'am.
-[man] Dear gods of heaven and earth…
I can see all the paths
in that place from here.
It is not with my eyes I see!
The gods of heaven and earth
are leading me by the hand!
Those who follow me
shall continue to live.
[Nam-gyu] Min-su.
-[Seon-nyeo] Get in my way and you'll die!
-Have you ever killed anyone?
Hey, there's no time.
If you can't do it, switch teams.
You're damn good at hiding.
Min-su.
I looked everywhere for you last night,
but I couldn't find you.
Where were you hiding?
Hm?
Were you that scared of me?
It's good that you hid yourself.
Well done.
That fucking bitch thought
she was Wonder Woman or something.
That goddamn bitch treated me
like a fucking idiot, and she…
-[snickers]
-[dark music]
Did you see it?
Damn. You saw it, didn't you?
But you stayed hidden like a fucking rat
and just watched?
You should've helped her.
That fucking bitch liked you.
Aw.
Min-su.
I like that look in your eyes right now.
Keep that look when you go in there,
and just go for it.
[knife clatters]
Thanos, that fucking bastard, is dead.
So is everyone else in our group.
It's just you and me now.
I'll be really lonely if you die too.
[breathes heavily]
So be a man this time, Min-su. Okay?
[knife clanks]
[imitating Thanos in English]
You can do it, my bro, Min-su.
Min-su.
See you again, Min-su.
[laughs]
[Myung-gi in Korean] Jun-hee.
Switch with me.
You take the key.
That's how we'll both survive.
Mind your own business.
I'll take care of myself.
How do I do that?
I know you won't be able
to do anything with the knife.
Don't act like you know
everything about me.
Maybe I don't, but I do know one thing.
You can't kill anyone.
Give me the knife.
I'll take someone out as quickly as I can,
and then come find you.
I will protect you and the baby, Jun-hee.
Is it easy for you to kill someone?
I would
kill everyone here if it meant
leaving here with you and the money.
[Jun-hee] To protect my baby,
I'd do anything too.
Then…
you kill me.
I'll come find you once the game begins.
Stab me with that knife and get out.
Then you and the baby can live.
[Yong-sik] Give me the knife.
-[Yong-sik sighs]
-[Geum-ja inhales]
[Geum-ja] I'll switch teams
with someone else instead.
We can stay together and--
Mom,
you have bad knees.
Once we go in there,
those people will come at us
with their knives.
If we go around hand in hand,
we'll both die.
No, you won't be able to do it.
How could you kill a person with this?
Even as a kid, you always let other kids
beat you up like a fool
whenever you got into a fight.
You've never hurt anyone, not even once.
What about you?
Can you go and kill someone with that?
Dad beat you all the time,
but you couldn't even fight back.
I'll do it.
I'll… try.
-[both breathe shakily]
-[tense music]
[in English] Thank you.
[Yeong-sam] Nice. [laughs]
[Player 192 exhales excitedly]
[Player 192 in Korean]
Thanks a bunch. [laughs]
Excuse me, would you like to switch with…
[music intensifies]
[Dae-ho] Listen to me.
If you switch teams with me,
I'll stay with you
and protect you until the end, okay?
But you'd have to kill someone too.
[yells] Will you just…
Just leave that to me.
I can still stay with you.
[gasps]
Please trust me. I'll keep my promise.
Okay?
[sighs in frustration]
[breath trembling]
[mumbling] Fuck.
What? What's your problem with me?
Why do you keep looking at me like that?
Want to blame me for everything?
What did I do so wrong?
We wouldn't have won.
We wouldn't have won anyway.
-Fuck,
-[box thuds]
stop looking at me like that!
It's not my fault!
If we had fought
the other damn side instead,
we could have won.
We could have won the fight
and then the vote!
It's your fault.
They all died
because of your ridiculous plan!
It's you!
You're the one who fucking killed them!
[breathing heavily]
[solemn music]
[woman on PA] The game
will begin momentarily.
Blue Team,
please get ready to enter the arena.
Let me repeat.
The game will begin momentarily.
[Captain] What happened to Choi?
He didn't show.
I talked to him on the phone earlier.
An urgent family matter came up.
All of a sudden?
I know.
[Captain] Maybe he chickened out.
People who act all tough and loud like him
are actually the biggest wimps.
It's for the best.
He's just a booze-chugging freeloader.
[solemn music]
Mom, stay well hidden.
I'll get it over with
and then come find you.
I'll find you and protect you.
Yong-sik.
Whenever your dad got drunk,
he always threatened to kill me.
But who kicked the bucket first?
Dad.
So do you really think
I'm gonna die in here?
[whispering] Besides, I also have a weapon
for emergencies.
So don't worry about me.
Focus on yourself.
Do whatever it takes to survive,
and we'll get out of here together, okay?
Yes.
Keep your word.
I promise I'll find you.
[eerie music]
[man] Shit…
-[door thuds]
-[players gasp]
-[timer beeps]
-[woman on PA] The taggers
will enter in two minutes.
[Jeong-dae] Listen up, people.
Instead of hiding,
let's spread out and find the exit.
Whoever finds the exit first
will shout and let everyone know!
Good idea! Let's help each other
and get out of here alive!
[child's voice on PA]
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play ♪
♪ Don't let your hair give you away ♪
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your clothes give you away ♪
Don't let your toe give you away ♪
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play
Don't let your hair… ♪
Want to do it together?
Do what?
-[Nam-gyu chuckles]
-[tense music]
You think the blue vests
will just let you kill them?
Of course not.
They'll really fucking resist.
[whispering] It'll be much easier
if we attack them together.
[child's voice on PA]
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play ♪
♪ Don't let your clothes give you away ♪
Are you all right?
[Hyun-ju] Ms. Geum-ja. Jun-hee.
Come with me.
[child's voice on PA]
♪ Hide, hide, it's time to play ♪
♪ Don't let your hair give you away ♪
-[Hyun-ju] Be careful.
-[Geum-ja] Okay.
[Nam-gyu] I'm not looking for
a relationship here.
Just a one-night stand, so to speak.
When you stabbed Thanos, you were
fucking awesome.
[child's voice on PA]
♪ Hide, hide… ♪
[timer beeps]
[woman on PA] Red Team,
please enter the arena.
Come on.
Hm?
[imitating Thanos in English]
Let's get it!
[music intensifies]
[in Korean] It's your fault.
[intense music]
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song